Lili Liang

813 Mitchel Field Way •Garden City•New York•(516)728-8687•livialiang1230@hotmail.com

PROFILE:

M.B.A. in Marketing Candidate, with three years of demonstrated experience in marketing and communicating with a proven ability to enhance profits; fast learning, hard working, and has proven experience in customer service, management, communication and sales that is committed to results. Seeking a position in the field of marketing.

EDUCATION:

Frank G Zarb School of Business, Hofstra University-Hempstead, New York

Master of Buiness Administration in Marketing, GPA: 3.91

Required Courses: Accounting, Fiance, Information System, Management, International Business, International marketing, Consumer Behavior, Advanced Quantitative Analysis for managers, Advertising, Pricing theory, etc.

Nanjing University of Posts and Telecommunications-Nanjing, China

Bachelor of Management in Marketing

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Pollster, Hofstra University/News 12 poll

Sep.2013-Nov.2013

• Worked in Hofstra Marketing Department with Channel 12 News, calling residents in Long Island to gather their opinions for marketing research.

VIP Customer Manager, China Telecom Corp. Ltd., Zhuhai Subsidiary

Jul. 2011-Feb. 2012

- Served two big enterprises such as Zhuhai Public Transportation Group Co., Ltd. and Zhuhai Education Bureau
- Successfully sold 1100 SIM Cards within one month after taking over the two enterprises and increased almost 2,500,000 RMB revenue for our company which doubled the annual sales of a employee.

Intern, China Telecom Corp. Ltd., Zhuhai Subsidiary

Aug. 2010-Sep. 2010

- Searched product information in the industry to make PowerPoints for industry report at conferences.
- Helped to develop marketing plan for 3G product and regularly visited VIP customers, including Government Informatization Office, Customs and Exit-Entry Management Division, etc.

Receptionist, McDonald's China

Sep. 2009-Nov. 2009

• Sold the concessionary cards, promoted parties for children and broadcasted for the store; quarterly decorated the facade in alignment with different marketing themes to marketing demands.

MARKETING PROJECTS:

- Worked on a international marketing plan from demographic analysis, psychographic analysis, local economy analysis to marketing mix strategy to market a newest innovation "Snorcare"-a full-face snorkeling mask that allows people to breathe naturally underwater to Indonesia.
- Class group assignment to devise a marketing plan for a luxurious mask. We made a survey to find out the market needs and used SWOT analysis to evaluate our marketing strategy. We also did some financial analysis to calculate the break-even point, marketing budget and sales forecast.

Skills:

- Computer: Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Language: Fluency in English and Mandarin (Oral and Written)
- Social Media: Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn,Instagram,Wechat,Weibo